[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["46.4 percent"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Did you agree that when Mitt Romney said that 47 percent of Americans are victims who basically scrounge off the state?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, mathematically the number was right, 46.4 percent of the people pay no federal income tax.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "PERCENT": ["47 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "What are you guys going to do about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, Piers, I'd rather be ahead than behind right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "WDT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "So this campaign has got to regroup, refocus and do something pretty sharp, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, I'm not nearly that pessimistic at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I am great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob McDonnell"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "I mean what is the view from the Democrats' side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, obviously, I mean, Bob McDonnell, bless his heart for trying his best to put on a still upper lip.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "POS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "So what do you have to say to that, Jennifer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, you know, first of all, redistribution, Barack Obama saying that he wants to make sure we have a fair society and we have Mitt Romney who's in favor of obviously redistributing up.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Not withstanding Mitt Romney's capacity for gaffes, which is clear and present, and causing them problems, if you take the bigger picture, why should any president in America be re-elected when unemployment is over 8 percent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, because the trajectory is right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "PERCENT": ["8 percent"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What do we know about both these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, first, let's start with the Guantanamo detainee.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stevens"], "LOCATION": ["Libya", "Tripoli", "Libya"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "NN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Where does this leave us in terms of going forward in the investigation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, look, there is no question that given -- you know, when I had been in Libya, in Tripoli, and met with Ambassador Stevens, he had acknowledged to me in a long conversation that in fact there was an increase of extremism in eastern Libya.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Do you feel, from all we're now hearing, that he was properly protected or should there have been more done for him there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "You know, it's hard to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stevens"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Well, while there is a lot of uncertainty about who exactly killed Ambassador Stevens, there's no doubt that al Qaeda and the Islamic Maghreb, which is the group they're talking about, is something we should be losing a lot of sleep over.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Isn't that so the migration was fighting either with al Qaeda or offshoot groups and then wind up moving into Libya?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "There was more of that that's much less true of al Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb than others.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Or is it a sort of amorphous series of terror cells around the world now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "There's really not much of a center structure to it anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "You're seeing this kind of ongoing and increasing instability if al Qaeda is still operating with these cells?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I don't -- I mean I think that this goes in kind of a sign.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "If he was -- if you take out all the rhetoric, if you take out all the gaffe element and the rhetoric, and you cut to his principle point that he claims he's been making a lot on the stump which is that, you know, a lot of people in America, mainly the ones who vote for Barack Obama don't much tax, they don't pay income tax, and are basically living off government handouts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, that particularly argument is not one that I would have made, to tell you the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Is it -- is it accurate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Well, no, I don't think it is accurate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Was it 10 trillion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "I don't remember what the number was precisely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What was the counter point you were going to come back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "UDLOW: I want to say a couple of things on this Romney stuff, I think sort of ripped it apart earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bain"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "And the reason has to be Mitt Romney, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Yes, I mean, the joke has been that he needs to hire a management consultant from Bain to try to rescue his campaign.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["47 percent"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "WRB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Why is he proving to be right now anyway so haphazard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "RISTOFF: I think that part of it is that he spent six years now effectively in a Republican primary bubble, talking to people where everybody sort of thinks that the 47 percent is this parasitic group in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Why did he not want to say that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Perhaps he just doesn't like those numbers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last century"], "PERSON": ["Reagan", "Reagan"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "I'm surprised that on all of the statistical information available, only one I think incumbent president in history has been re-elected with unemployment over eight percent, and that was FDR?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "As an old Reagan guy, literally, in the last century, I worked for Reagan in his first term.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "On the redistribution thing, what is redistribution and why has it become a dirty word?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I don't see why it should b.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Final word, Nick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Let me push back at the notion that taxes make all the difference in growth.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 500, "question": "In very simple terms, what happened here with you and your ex-husband?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Um, he got kicked out of the country and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "He had his visa revoked?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "He had his visa -- yes exactly, he had his visa revoked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "He is German?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "He is German.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "You went over to France with the children to see him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "I went to visit them, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Is this indefinitely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Therefore the French have decided everyone stays there apart from you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "EX", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Well, the American judge said this, the California judge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "How do you feel about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I'm beside myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "How is it possible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I have long been interested in the rights of children in contested divorce cases.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "This is an American judge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "It's an American judge, a woman, American judge who decided that it would be best for everybody if the children moved out of this country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Do they know what is going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I think they have an idea, but they don't really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "How old are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Three and five.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Were you amicable at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Not -- not so much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Have you tried to appeal to him and his humanity over this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "What does he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "He says no, we are going through the court system.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "120919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What is the next legal step that you can take on Kelly's behalf?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Well, I think we have to find a very good established lawyer who emphasizes the rights of children to find the right vehicle, whether it be a federal court lawsuit protecting the interests of the children as American citizens, whether it be an appeal in the California courts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly"]}}]